A resolution censoring Representative Rashida Tlaib for anti-Semitic activity, sympathizing with terrorist organizations, and leading an insurrection at the United States Capitol complex.
Whereas in May 2019, Rashida Tlaib said that she celebrated the Holocaust and felt a calming feeling when thinking about the genocide of millions of Jews.
Whereas in 2020, Rashida Tlaib retweeted an illustration with the caption,
From the river to the sea, Palestine will be free.
And this Palestine Liberation Organization PLO slogan has been adopted by Hamas and calls for the elimination of Israel and death to all Jews.
Whereas in September 2022, Rashida Tlaib, as a member of the Congressional Progressive Caucus, displayed her disdain for Israel, saying,
You cannot claim to hold progressive values, yet back Israel's apartheid government.
Whereas instead of denouncing the horrors of Hamas, slaughtering Israelis, and demanding the release of all hostages held by Hamas,
Rashida Tlaib stated on October 8, 2023,
The path to the future must include lifting the blockade, ending the occupation, and dismantling the apartheid system.